bca-europe.com 2014-05-26

# Privacy policy - BCA Group

BCA's privacy policy is to respect and protect the privacy of visitors to the BCA web site and subscribers to any email updates from the web site. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. It will assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services.

The data we collect  
We do request personal information such as your name, email address, company details, etc which you can choose to provide when you complete and submit a web form on the BCA web site. We collect this information to help us more accurately respond to your enquiry. You are under no obligation to provide any personal data if you don't want to.  Information collected from the registration form on the BCA Digital Sales Guide is used to keep you informed on BCA sales and/or products and services, on which you have requested information.

We also use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our web site, new services and other information we think you will find valuable. If you choose to opt out of receiving any such communications from us, please email us at [news@bca-group.com](mailto:news@bca-group.com)with "Unsubscribe" in the subject line.

In the future BCA may decide to also collect aggregate information from all web site visitors. This aggregate data would only be used to customize BCA web content to deliver a better experience for our users and will in no way personally identify you.

Use of IP Address  
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. On occasions, we collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to analyse aggregate information, and to audit the use of our site.

Use of Cookies  
What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard you will find them at most major web sites.

By showing how and when visitors use our site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed and this information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use cookies to better understand and improve areas of the BCA web site that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to the BCA web site always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the BCA web site may not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies.

Use of clear GIFs  
A clear GIF (Graphics Interchange Format) or pixel tag (also known as a 'Web beacon') is a line of code placed on some of our web pages and/or in e-mails which, in a similar way to our use of cookies above, allow us to analyse the specific usage patterns of visitors.

Supplementary Information  
We may acquire information about individuals from other sources and add such information to our house files.

Disclosure  
We will not publish, give, sell or rent your information to anyone, ever. However, we reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) BCA's rights or property, other users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Links to Other Sites/ "Public" Areas  
You should be aware that when you are on the BCA web site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from BCA web site pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may significantly differ from that of BCA. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

Security  
Protecting the security of all personally-identifiable information associated with our guests is of the utmost concern to us. Once we receive your transmission, we will take reasonable precautions to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our users' personal information and maintain their privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of such personal information.

Privacy Policy for Minors  
BCA does not knowingly collect information from children. If you are under 13, please do not provide any personal information to us.

The List Owner (the Data Controller)  
The List Owner and Data Controller is British Car Auctions Ltd, Expedier House, Portsmouth Road, Hindhead, Surrey GU26 6TJ. www.bca-europe.com

Access to your own data  
To be provided with a copy of your own personal data that we collect online and maintain in our database, and to contest and correct inaccuracies, or request that your personal data be deleted, please send an e-mail and we will action your request. To unsubscribe BCA email communications please email us at [news@bca-group.com](mailto:news@bca-group.com)with "Unsubscribe" in the subject, and we will take you off the list.  
  
Your Acceptance of the Terms of this Privacy Policy  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the BCA Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Disclaimer and Legal Notice  
The following are the terms and conditions of use of this website and its services. If you do not accept these conditions, you must not use this website or services.

The content on this website is provided 'as is', and British Car Auctions Ltd ('BCA') gives no representation or warranty as to the accuracy of the content and assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in it or the effect it has upon your computer. This site includes links to other sites on the Internet. BCA cannot vouch for the suitability or accuracy of the content of those sites and so you use them at your own risk. Any references to linked sites or to third-party companies, products or services by name does not constitute or infer its endorsement by BCA.

The information available on the site might from time to time be incomplete, out of date or inaccurate. BCA reserves the right at any time and without prior notice to make changes and corrections to the material on the site or to make parts or all of this site unavailable at any time without notice.

BCA disclaims all liability in respect of all information and its provision, and shall not be liable for any loss or damages suffered as a result of any use of the site. Although BCA aims to keep it up-to-date, it do not guarantee its accuracy. BCA does try to make this site as useful as possible, none of the material it contains is professional advice or a substitute for it, and can not be relied upon as such.

Unless specified to the contrary, the contents of this website and these pages are protected by copyright. The authors and creators of the material on the website assert their moral rights. The BCA, BCA Direct, Auction View, Commercial Auction View, BCA Smart Prepared, BCA Live Online and all other BCA product and/or service logos and contents of this website (including text, design and graphics) are trademarked and copyrighted materials of BCA. All rights are reserved. They may not be used, transmitted or reproduced unless in accordance with prior written instructions issued by BCA. No use, transmission or reproduction is permitted other than the following:

Permission is given for the downloading and temporary storage of pages where indicated on such pages, for the sole purpose of individual viewing on a standalone PC or monitor. Such pages may be printed, but these may not be further reproduced, copied or transmitted in any way to those other than the initial individual user. You may not reproduce any other part of the website including, but not limited to, the structure, overall style and program code.

These conditions of use are governed by English law and any dispute connected with this site is subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. BCA may change these conditions of use from time to time. You will be bound by changes even if you do not re-visit this page to re-read this notice.  
Please note that these are BCA's terms and conditions of use and if you do not accept these conditions, you must not use this website or services.

British Car Auctions Ltd  
Privacy Policy & Legal Notice - Version 1.0 20.08.2004
